— Main Menu —About CHA \- Who We Are \- Member Companies About Programs \- About Discount Health Plans \- 2017 Discount Health Care Programs Report \- FAQ Code of Conduct Newsroom \- Newsroom \- Blog Contact Join Members’ Area

CHA Privacy Policy
==================

#### Privacy Statement Information Collection

As you browse and review Consumer Health Alliance, (CHA) CHA Website, you do so anonymously. We do not collect any personal information, including your e-mail address. We do track information based on your IP address. We do this to log CHA Website statistics that we use in evaluating who visits our CHA Website and how long they spend here. We also track the type of computer you are using and the operating system, as well as your browser name and version.

The only collection of personal information occurs in the 'Contact Us' area of our web CHA Website. This is voluntary information that you enter and submit to us via an HTML-based web form.  

#### Use of Submitted Information

Consumer Health Alliance could use the personal information you submit to gather demographic data about you as well as respond to your question or comment.  

#### Links to Other Websites

Consumer Health Alliance, CHA Website contains external links to other websites on the internet without any warranty or representation with regard to the products or services which may be advertised or promoted at these CHA Websites. Consumer Health Alliance, is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content found at these other internet websites.

© 2018 Consumer Health Alliance (CHA)  
For more information call 1 (800) 550-1242
